Did they leave?
他們回去了嗎
The reporter's gone home too.
記者也回去了唷
Yeah. Today wasn't a good day for an interview.
也是啦 畢竟今天不適合採訪
Leaving all this aside.
我說 這個事件妳就就此收手吧
Wh-Why?
為 為什麼啊
For decades, that building has been at the center of all kinds of rumors.
那棟大樓從十幾年前開始 就流傳著各種傳聞
There was also the bloodstain of a missing police officer from five years ago.
那裡五年前還出現過 一名下落不明的警察的血跡
And now, they're launching a major investigation into a mugger who sought refuge in it? That's not normal.
結果這次又因為有搶劫犯躲在裡面 所以要強制搜查 這真的很不尋常
This is no job for a rookie to take on.
這不是妳這種新人該做的工作
Hand it over to Himura Atari. He's a veteran.
接下來就交給像火村這樣的老手吧
No.
不
This is my story.
這是我的報導
If I force her out, she probably goes out and covers the story in her own time.
如果我強行讓她退出的話 她很有可能會請帶薪假擅自跑去採訪
Let me do it, Chief!
我做到了唷 主編
I have exposed a misdeed, Chief!
我揭露了一個惡行哦 主編
Here's photographic evidence, Chief!
這是證據的照片哦 主編
But she's too good for me to just fire her over it.
不過再怎麼說 她也是個開除了會很可惜的人才
Fine. Then I'll compromise.
我知道了 那我們就各退一步吧
Stick to the occult angle as an occult reporter
妳最多只能作為一名神秘學記者
and tell the story of diviner Corpse God.
去近距離接觸占卜師屍神殿
Don't take it any further than that.
但是妳不准超出自己的職責範圍
Don't investigate anything beyond his fortune-telling.
也不准去調查占卜以外的事情
Aw…
唔…
And pulling that face isn't going to do anything.
就算妳做出這種表情我也不會同意
In exchange, if anything else comes up,
不過 如果發生了什麼事的話
I'll give you first dibs on exclusive news.
那裡可是離獨家新聞最近的地方哦
Okay, but…
雖然是這樣沒錯…
But what?
妳有什麼不滿意的嗎
You don't trust your hunch that Polka Shinoyama is at the center of all this?
妳不是說四乃山波爾卡是關鍵人物嗎 妳該不會對自己的直覺沒有自信吧
Heh…
呵呵呵…
Don't think so little of me, Chief Editor!
可別小看我唷 主編
I'll definitely prove that Polka Shinoyama is the key player in this case.
我一定會漂亮地證明出 四乃山波爾卡就是這起事件的關鍵
Oh yes.
我要上囉
Wait. Don't forge any evidence or anything, okay?
等等 妳絕對不能捏造新聞哦
(Episode 15: The Vampire) By the way, young lady.
(#15 The Vampire -吸血鬼-) 對了 大小姐
I got those things you asked me for.
您另外拜託我買的東西 我已經買回來了
Thanks.
辛苦你了
So
話說
what's in there, really?
那到底是什麼啊
Something to cover my room rent.
你就把這當作是我租房的費用吧
Magic storing stones!
是魔留石
STONES THAT HAVE MAGIC STORED IN THEM, KNOWN AS JEWELS IN THIS WORLD Raw gems?
(蘊含魔力的石頭 也就是這邊的世界的寶石) 這是寶石的原石嗎
I had Xiaoyu go around to the accessory shops and general stores to buy them.
是我拜託小幽 跑遍各式各樣的商店買來的
Are you sure I can have them?
我可以收下嗎
It's fine.
可以的
After all, the real Polka was saved thanks to you.
畢竟你救了真正的波爾卡
So she knows this Polka's a fake.
原來大小姐也知道 這個波爾卡是假的嗎
And he saved the real Polka?
他救了真正的波爾卡…
What does that mean?
這是什麼意思
Also, what is he going to do with all those raw gems?
而且 他要用這麼多的原石去做什麼
So? So what can you do with all these?
對了對了 有這麼多的原石 可以做什麼呀
Well…
我想想
There's one major thing I can think of doing.
我覺得至少可以做一件大事
I know what the first thing I'm going to do is.
但是 我已經想好首先要做什麼了
That is…
那就是…
What's that mean?
那是什麼意思
So what do we do about our problem now?
然後 問題就是 我們接下來該怎麼做了
I contacted Clarissa,
雖然我已經跟克拉麗莎聯絡過了
but what about the corpse in the basement passage?
可是地下通道裡的屍體該怎麼處理啊
A corpse? What's this about?
屍體 他們在說什麼
For the time being, let's just make sure it's not discovered.
總之 我們就先暫時裝作 屍體不在我們這裡吧
I guess it's a bartender named Nishida who worked for Clarissa.
不過那具屍體八成就是克拉麗莎店裡 那個叫西田的調酒師
Urai returned to Clarissa's bar during the investigation.
雖然我們也讓裏井趁搜查混亂的時候 回到克拉麗莎的店裡了
Oh, so he works at Clarissa's place.
原來那個人是克拉麗莎店裡的人啊
Immediately after Nishida's body was dumped here, the police showed up.
西田的屍體被放在那裡之後 警察馬上就來了
In other words, are the police in cahoots with whoever killed Nishida?
這就代表 警察和殺害西田的傢伙 是一伙的吧
Darn it.
糟糕
We'll talk more later!
我們下次再說吧
I'm going to slip out the back, so take care of the rest for me!
我先從後門溜了 之後就交給你們了
If you need anything, contact me.
有事的話記得聯絡我
See you.
我走了
Oh, okay.
啊 好
Wow, this all looks delicious!
哇 這些菜看起來好好吃呀
I've always thought so, you're a really good chef.
我從以前就一直覺得 你真的很擅長料理耶
Just doing my job.
畢竟這也是我工作的一部分
Thanks for the food.
我開動了
Hey.
嗨
Hello.
你們好
You're eating?
你們在吃晚餐嗎
Sorry for interrupting.
抱歉
Are you guys looking for the mugger too?
刑警先生你們也是來找搶劫犯的嗎
No. We're still on the Solitaire case.
不 我們是來調查雪天鴉的事的
Then, let me get straight to the point.
那麼 我就開門見山地問了
Why did Solitaire come to this building?
為什麼雪天鴉會到這裡來
You know the answer to that, don't you?
你應該知道吧
The reason why Solitaire came here…
雪天鴉為什麼會來這裡…
This policeman shouldn't know anything about that mark.
這個警察應該不知道 那個標記的事才對
No, I have no idea why.
不 我也不知道呢
Ah!
啊
P-Polka!
波 波爾卡
What I wrote down for this detective before…
我之前寫給這個警察的 其實就是…
There's only one thing connecting you and Solitaire.
我目前知道的就只有 你跟雪天鴉之間有唯一的關聯
The mark Solitaire drew on his airship.
那就是飛艇上的標記
You can get in touch with Mr. Hosorogi,
你是不是能聯絡上細呂木先生
can't you?
對吧
Can you let me see him?
可以讓我見一見細呂木先生嗎
So in other words,
那也就是說
you didn't believe my fortune-telling skills from the beginning.
你打從一開始 就不相信我的占卜 對吧
If you don't believe in me,
對於不相信我的人
and I can't form a relationship of mutual trust with you,
對於不能與我們建立信賴關係的人
then there's nothing I can say.
我沒有什麼好說的…
Hey.
喂
We've come too far, and you still want to weasel out of this?
事到如今 你覺得你還能蒙混過去嗎
What can be known is that
可以知道的是
PANIC! THE MYSTERIOUS ORGANIZATION HIDDEN IN SOCIETY! the danger is drawing near.
(恐慌!!潛藏於社會的神秘組織 ) 危險正在慢慢地逼近我
How far can my hands reach?
我的手究竟可以伸向何處
There might be souls that I miss.
這世上可能還存在著 我沒能觸及到的靈魂
That's why I must be cautious.
所以我必須十分謹慎
How about you come clean with me, boy?
我們可以推心置腹地談一談嗎 少年
FOOD Food…
吃飯…
Prove to me you're not involved with the underbelly of the police force.
你能證明你自己 沒有被警察內部的黑暗給侵蝕嗎
Your answer is on the piece of paper that guided you earlier.
答案就在之前引導你的那張紙條上
"If you still believe in me,
"如果你還相信自己"
then keep pursuing it."
"那你就繼續前進吧"
That's from the person you want to see.
這是你想見的人所留下的話
Geez.
真是的
There have been too many things today, one after another.
今天真是發生了不少事呢
But for now, I have to sort that out.
總之我得先整理一下情報
Hmm?
咦
I don't remember ordering any packages.
我不記得我有在網路上買過什麼東西
Don't tell me it's Arase.
該不會是荒瀨吧
Mr. Higuro?
冰黑…先生
Why would he be here now?
為什麼他會在這種時候過來…
"Why," indeed.
你猜猜看呀
Aren't you going to let him in?
你為什麼不開門呢
Mr. Higuro is a lonely guy,
冰黑先生可是很怕寂寞的
so he might cry, you know?
他都要哭了哦
But, you might be the one who ends up in tears.
不過 等一下哭得更厲害的 說不定是你呢
Hang on. I'll be right up.
稍等一下 我馬上就過去
So Polka Shinoyama really is in contact with inspector Hosorogi?
四乃山波爾卡果然 有在跟細呂木搜查官聯絡嗎
I don't know.
誰知道呢
But either way, he's right.
不管怎樣 就像他所說的
First, I'll investigate the fortune-telling paper.
我們目前得先調查一下 他在占卜時給我的那張紙條
Aren't we acting immediately?
我們現在不馬上行動嗎
I'd love to.
我也想這麼做
But if we're not careful, they could catch wind of our activities.
但是草率地行動 可是會暴露我們這邊的情況的
This situation is really unbearable.
連自己所在的組織都無法信任
We can't even trust our own organization.
這還真是諸事不順啊
You said it.
就是說啊
I fully understand why Mr. Hosorogi disappeared.
我現在完全能理解 細呂木先生為什麼要消失了
THE KEY IS BEHIND THE 1-383 MIRROR.
(鑰匙在1-383號鏡子的背面)
Darn it.
可惡
It's starting to rain again.
又開始下雨了啊
Long time no see.
好久不見
What're you doing here after all this?
事到如今你還來找我做什麼
Haha. You hate me so much.
哈哈 看來我徹底被你給討厭了呢
Isn't that obvious?
這還用說嗎
You must at least know that I'm working for Clarissa now.
你應該知道 我現在在克拉麗莎那裡工作吧
Sure.
是啊
That's why I'm here.
所以我才會過來找你呀
You figure it out?
你已經察覺了嗎
Did you turn Nishida into a mugger?
是你讓西田變成搶劫犯的嗎
You thought it for a moment, didn't you?
你剛才在回答前 是不是稍微思考了一下
You were choosing your words.
你在思考自己該說什麼
Right?
沒錯吧
Whether to say "dead body" or "mugger."
我猜你是在想說 屍體和搶劫 你該說哪一個
So it really was you.
果然是你這傢伙…
I figured you knew about the dead body.
你果然知道屍體的事
Pain is good. It dulls a person's judgement.
疼痛是一種可以讓人 失去判斷力的好東西
It makes you fall for questions you would normally never fall for.
套不出來的話 通常都可以用這種方法套出來
All the more for someone who fears pain, like you.
尤其是像你這樣害怕疼痛的人
How did you manage to hide the body?
在那種情況下 你們是怎麼把屍體藏起來的呢
My employer is willing to use any means necessary
我的雇主
to deal with all the people associated with the building you're using.
他想通過光明正大的力量 來擊垮與那棟大樓有關的人
So we need the body of the mugger to be found in that building.
所以沒能在那棟大樓裡發現 搶劫犯的屍體 會讓我們很難辦啊
Are you sure you should be saying all this in front of me?
你把這些事都說出來真的沒關係嗎
Of course.
那當然
You're smart, so you understand why, don't you?
聰明的你應該明白吧
Now that you've heard it, you're all out of options.
既然你已經聽到了 那你就已經別無選擇了
Mr. Higuro.
冰黑先生
He might still have options.
他或許還有別的選擇
Misaki?
美咲
Huh, where's Misaki?
咦 美咲呢
She went to get Takumi.
她去接匠了
Miss Clarissa called to speak with him.
因為克拉麗莎小姐打電話來說要找他
So the Shinjuku intermediary agency
新宿的仲介屋
figured out what I was up to.
他們已經猜到我的動向了嗎
Did you receive some kind of training?
妳是不是接受過某種訓練啊
It doesn't make sense that you're stronger than me with that body.
不然妳那具身體的力氣 怎麼會比我還要大
I'm a growing girl!
因為我還在正在發育嘛
So close.
就差一點呢
Nobody's ever jumped over me before.
妳還是第一個敢從我頭頂跳過去的人
No joke.
我並不是在嘲諷妳
That was really close.
而是剛才是真的很危險啊
Misaki.
美咲
Hey, Misa--
喂 美…咲
Oh dear.
哎呀哎呀
Now Shibuya and Shinjuku are very likely to have a conflict.
這樣一來 澀谷和新宿 很有可能要發生衝突了
Great.
那也不錯啊
If I get to fight with more kids like this, I'll gladly welcome it.
能和更多像她一樣的孩子戰鬥的話 我可是會很高興的
I'd rather not.
我就算了
Hey.
喂
I'm really sorry.
非常抱歉
There was a slight hiccup.
我們這邊出了點異常
I'll report to you later.
事後我會再向您匯報
Under the protection of Sabaramond, there can be no failure.
在塞巴拉隆多的庇護之下 是不存在失敗的
Are you sure it was okay to use the gems for that?
話說 就這樣用掉寶石真的可以嗎
Yes. What I can do is limited.
嗯 畢竟我的能力範圍有限
I know what the first thing I'm going to do is.
我已經決定好最先該做什麼了
Having Misaki evolve into new species.
那就是美咲的種族進化
Not only will it widen my hands of protection,
只靠我伸手去保護他人是不夠的
but I want to increase the number of allies who can help me protect everyone.
我想要增加能跟我一起 守護大家的夥伴
Now Misaki is no longer a zombie.
現在的美咲已經不再是僵屍了
She's a vampire.
而是吸血鬼的幼體
I see.
原來如此
It's so weird that I was killed but didn't die!
被殺了卻沒有死 這可真是不可思議呢
But thanks to that, I think I'm getting used to it.
但是多虧有這個能力 真是讓我越來越適應了
Is this what rebirth feels like?
這就是重生的感覺嗎
No.
不對
Nothing's changed.
我還是沒有變
I've always been a monster.
因為我本來就不是人啊
TEN YEARS AGO You don't smile much, do you?
(十年前) 妳從來都沒笑過呢
I bet you'd be a real charmer if you did, though.
妳笑起來肯定會很可愛
I want to smile.
我想笑
But I forgot how to.
可是 我已經忘記該怎麼笑了
What makes someone smile differs from person to person.
每個人感興趣的事情都不一樣
What if you try copying what other people seem to enjoy?
妳要不要試著去模仿別人 去做一些他們會樂在其中的事呢
Is there such a thing?
有這樣的事嗎
What other people seem to enjoy…
別人做起來會樂在其中的事…
I know.
有
What is it? I'll do what I can to help you.
是什麼 我來幫妳吧
Killing people.
殺人
Something landed on us.
好像有東西降落在車上面
Is it a pursuer?
是追兵嗎
Oh.
哎呀
They ran away.
他們不見了
I'll catch up!
不過我馬上就能追上他們
Huh?
咦
I guess it's hard to get airborne starting from the ground!
從下往上飛好像有點難呢
There they are!
啊 他們在那
That was close!
好險好險
But Polka is really amazing!
不過 波爾卡可真是厲害啊
Even though it's new to me,
雖然我是第一次飛
I can get around in the body like it's always been mine!
但我卻能無比順利地控制自己的身體
Being a vampire is great!
當吸血鬼真不錯
I like this!
我很滿意
By the way, Clarissa,
對了 克拉麗莎
I'm enjoying this right now!
我現在很開心哦
Besides killing people, I've found something else I enjoy!
我找到除了殺人之外 還能讓我感到高興的事了
I never knew that helping someone could get my heart racing like this!
為幫助他人而奔走 原來是如此地令人興奮啊
Or that challenging someone way stronger than me could be this thrilling!
挑戰比自己還要強的人 原來是如此地振奮人心啊
I know you're awake, Takumi.
我知道你已經醒了哦 匠
If you are really asleep,
如果你真的還在睡的話
then how about we peel the skin off your arm to wake you up?
為了叫醒你 我要不要把你手上的皮給剝開呢
All right!
知道了知道了
I'm awake, so just don't torture me!
我已經起來了 你不要再折磨我了
Oh, that's good.
太好了
Now you won't have to embarrass yourself in front of Agakura.
看來你不用在阿牙倉的人面前出醜了
That bean-pole there is an Agakura?
那位細竹竿小哥是阿牙倉的人嗎
"Bean-pole"? So funny.
居然說我是細竹竿… 你講話還真是復古呢
Granted, I am the tallest in the family.
我確實是我家裡長得最高的
How well-known our family is.
不過我們家還真是有名呢
Of course.
那當然
The Agakura is infamous in the underworld as an elite circle of crazies.
阿牙倉一家可是為數不多 在黑道上有名的危險人物啊
"Don't mess with the 'Crazy Bones Kagura' or the Agakura family."
不要招惹盡是邪教教徒與暴走族的 凶骨神樂和阿牙倉家族
You're the one who told me that, Mr. Higuro.
這些不都是你告訴我的嗎 冰黑先生
Yeah. That's right.
是啊 我確實有告訴過你
So I paid Agakura's guys to be on our side.
所以我就出錢 讓阿牙倉的人成為了我的夥伴
Just like you've allied with the Heilei.
就像你拉攏了黑雷一樣
Heilei?
黑雷
You don't look like you're playing dumb.
你看起來不是在裝傻呢
So Shinoyama doesn't completely trust you either.
看來四乃山也沒有完全信任你呢
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼啊
Isn't there a black-haired boy in your building?
你們那棟大樓裡 不是有個黑頭髮的男孩嗎
He's an assassin employed by the Shinoyama family.
他是四乃山家雇的暗殺者哦
Just when I was planting a listening device in that Takumi guy's place
我在匠的家裡安裝了竊聽器
to see if I could get more info on the corpse.
本來是打算調查屍體的情報的
Why? Why are they…
為什麼 為什麼那些傢伙…
Agakura!
阿牙倉
I have no reason to interfere with Agakura.
我沒有必要對阿牙倉的人出手
No.
不
I'm not a Heilei anymore.
我已經不是黑雷的人了
If I can get him out of here,
我現在把那個傢伙救出來
having that fake Polka owe me one isn't such a bad plan.
讓假波爾卡欠我一個人情也不錯
Why don't we pick up where we left off?
那麼 我們繼續討論之前的話題吧
You don't have a choice.
你已經別無選擇了
We made it that far, right?
我記得我之前是說到這裡吧
Hey.
我說
Doesn't he actually have two choices?
他不是還有兩個選擇嗎
Either he cooperates or he dies.
是協助我們 還是去死
Oh, he doesn't have that.
他是不會選擇去死的
Yeah, Takumi?
喂 匠
When death's staring you in the face, you easily abandon the "now."
你可是能夠為了保命而拋棄一切的
That head-mounted display you've got on proves that.
你頭上戴著的這個東西就是證據
When you were young and believed in the goodness of people.
從小你就相信人性本善
FATHER: IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT Yet you were betrayed by the world and your parents.
(爸爸：都是你的錯) 可你卻被世界和父母給背叛了
After that,
之後
you believed that evil was the correct path.
你就相信邪惡才是人之本性
So you joined the gang Sons of the Styx.
於是你就加入了三途川的餓鬼們
And then Arase crushed that gang, thereby destroying the value you'd placed in that.
當你們的組織被荒瀨給擊潰後 你的那份價值觀也隨之崩塌
Neither justice nor evil feel real to you.
無論是正義還是邪惡 對你來說都毫無實感
You…
你…
PLAY START developed a phobia of reality.
(PLAY START) 患上了現實恐懼症 我說得沒錯吧
The view of the world through your camera
你將透過鏡頭看到的場景
gives you peace of mind because it makes everything like a game.
全部都處理成遊戲裡的畫面 這樣就能讓你自己感到安心
It's a really sad story.
真是個悲慘的故事啊
Almost makes me want to cry.
我都要哭了
You sure know your stuff.
你可真是一清二楚呢
Well, I did appreciate your intel-gathering abilities.
因為我很欣賞你的情報收集能力
I'd thought if I had the chance, I might win you back over.
我還想說如果有機會的話 就要讓你再次為我所用
But it seems that Miss Kuraki values you very much.
可是倉木小姐似乎很中意你
Why would you live in that abandoned building?
既然如此 你為又什麼會住在那棟 有著黑歷史的大樓裡呢
I'd be so happy if you'd tell me that.
要是你能詳細地跟我講一下的話 我會很高興的
You don't want it to be game over yet, do you?
你不願意就這樣結束遊戲吧
CALL RECORDS I still can't get through to Kuruya's cell.
(通話記錄) 還是打不通
I've always wondered
我從以前就開始在懷疑
whether we can really trust that guy.
那個男人真的值得信賴嗎
As long as he's bound by fear, he's obedient.
他在被恐懼給束縛時就會順從我們
But when he's faced with an even greater fear, all bets are off.
不過要是他遇到更可怕的事情 那就不好說了
So it'll be bad if he's been captured by the enemy, right?
那麼 如果他被敵人給抓住了 那不就糟糕了嗎
We should've planted a self-destruct device on him.
要是我們有事先給他裝上 自爆裝置就好了
You're right. This is actually perfect timing.
是啊 不過這樣也正好
He needed other shackles besides fear.
他需要一個不同於恐懼的其他枷鎖
A new bond besides the one he has with us.
需要一個與我們不一樣的新關係
Haha, you got me.
哈哈 這可真是讓我傷腦筋啊
You're right that I'm afraid of being game over.
我的確很害怕遊戲結束
But giving in to you here and now would be a bad ending too.
但是就這樣屈服於你 也算是一種壞結局吧
Don't worry. I only grazed you.
放心吧 子彈只是稍微擦過去而已
In movies, getting shot in the arm or leg is treated like a minor injury.
雖然電影裡經常 將手腳受傷描寫成輕傷
In reality, if the bullet hit a major artery, you'd die of blood loss, you know?
但現實中要是傷到大血管 可是會失血致死的哦
And
反正
you'll end up talking in the end anyway.
你最後一定會告訴我們的
No secrets would be more important than your life.
畢竟對你來說沒有什麼祕密 是比性命還要重要的了
My friends' lives are much more valuable than any secret of mine.
對於我來說 沒有什麼秘密 是比朋友的性命還要重要的
Yes.
是啊
You're right.
你說得沒錯
Mr. Higuro.
冰黑先生
You feel like answering me now?
你願意說了嗎
Nobody likes the guy who goes through
大家通常會討厭那種
the whole movie but insisting, "That's not how it works in real life."
看電影時說裡面的劇情 一點都不真實的人
I agree with that.
我也同意這點
You think that's just a threat?
你覺得我只是在嚇你嗎
Something is off.
這種感覺真奇怪
I can tell he's afraid of pain.
雖然我能夠感覺到他對疼痛的害怕
But he's not afraid of death itself?
但我卻感覺不到他對死亡的恐懼
If I die,
如果我死了
bring me back to life, Polka.
波爾卡 也請你把我的靈魂給找回來
I had steamed meat dumplings for lunch,
我中午吃的是燒賣
but I only dipped them in mustard when eating.
可我吃燒賣時通常只沾芥末
SOY SAUCE
(醬油)
Feel like talking now?
你願意說了嗎
Maybe a little.
我也想稍微…
I want to be stubborn too.
我也想稍微逞一次強呢
Otherwise, I…
不然 我就…
wouldn't be able to take a step forward.
無法繼續前進了
I wish you'd held onto that stubbornness back when Arase was threatening you.
我倒是希望當初荒瀨威脅你時 你也能這麼有骨氣呢
I'll just say one thing.
我要先跟你說一下
This doesn't have to be you.
我們並不是非要你說不可
For example, it could be that girl who is always holding the stuffed shark.
舉例來說 那個抱著鯊魚玩偶的女孩也可以
Hey.
喂喂
Don't you know who she is?
你知道她是誰嗎
The Shinoyama family won't let you go.
四乃山家是不會放過你的
That's fine.
啊 沒關係 沒關係
Higher up will solve this for me.
上面會幫我解決的
Higher up?
上面嗎
So you can stop worrying and keep writhing around.
所以你就放心地躺著吧
Even if you die,
要是我不小心讓你死了
you can always be replaced.
我也能找到其他人來代替你的
I found a reason to save him.
我找到救他的理由了
If his death would put my young lady next in line,
要是這傢伙死了 下一個受害的就是大小姐了
then I'd better keep him alive to take the heat.
所以我希望 這傢伙能活下來作為替死鬼
Well, well.
哎呀
You also gave me a reason to kill you guys.
我也找到殺你們的理由了
If you'd do wrong to the Shinoyama,
如果說你們對四乃山家圖謀不軌的話
then you're my enemy.
那你們就是我的敵人
The Shinjuku mugging?
新宿的搶劫事件嗎
Yes.
是的
We went to investigate that building where Solitaire showed up.
我們去調查了雪天鴉去過的那棟大樓
Wait a minute.
等一下
I was never told…
這種事…
No, wait.
不 等等
The building where Solitaire showed up?
雪天鴉去過的大樓 是那棟嗎
The one where Hosorogi…
細呂木出事的…
You can look into it, but let me remind you,
我允許你調查 但你可要小心啊
don't let your emotions get the better of you.
千萬不能感情用事哦
If you go on a rampage,
要是你失控了
even I won't be able to cover for you.
我可就沒辦法罩住你了
I'll be fine.
沒事的
I have a lackey who'll keep me in the line even if he has to punch me to do it.
我有一位能及時把我打醒的部下
Come in.
進來吧
This is a nice chair.
這張椅子真不錯
You could say such a fine piece fits your responsibility.
可以說是一張與肩負的重任 相匹配的椅子
If you want to be famous, you're in the wrong place.
如果你是想出名的話 那你搞錯地方了
Phantom Solitaire.
怪人雪天鴉
(Episode 16: The Fake)
(#16 The Fake -虛偽-)